

# **Skills**

### **PRO SKILLS**

HTML/CSS
React Js
PHP
Laravel
Codeigniter
Javascript

### **PRE SKILLS**

Analytic
Creative
Energy
Teamwork

# **Organization History**

#### **OSMA**

As a chief

### OSIS

Comunication and foreign language division

## Language

### Language Skill

Indonesia Inggris B. Arab



### Contact

- ★ Bogor, Cigombong
- © 085156881208
- ➤ Rinaldiputra0812@gmail.com
- in Rinaldi Putra
- @ Rinaldi.ptra

# RINALDI PUTRA

WFR DEVELOPER

### **Profile**

I am someone who is very interested in the world of technology, especially in the field of programming. -+ 3 years of experience as a programmer makes my skills in technology increase, learning new things is a must in order to balance the rapid technological advances And I am a person who really prioritizes soft skills, this is shown by the formation of a positive attitude in I am honest, disciplined, responsible, able to work with a team, and able to work under pressure

# **Experience**

## WEB DEVELOPER

Falcon Picture | November - 2022 - Present

- 1. Build Api and web apps for E-learning application
- 2. Slicing disign from figma to html
- 3. Build CMS for E-learning application
- 4. Connect to api Chat GPT for feature AI on E-learning

# WEB DEVELOPER

Honda | August - 2022 - Oktober - 2022

- 1. Creating applications for internal cooperatives
- 2. Creating unit testing scenarios

### WEB DEVELOPER

PT. Bringin Inti Teknologi | Augus 2021 - August 2022

Here I was assigned to be a web developer, assisting the development of existing applications or creating new applications. And these are some of the applications that I have worked on:

- 1. Join in developing Frontend pasar.id application
- 2. Build a new company profile(bitcorp.id)
- 3. Slicing from figma design to html css bootstrap javascript
- 5. Build company profile management application
- 6. Redesign frontend E-office application
- 5. Join in developing device monitoring applications

# FRONTEND DEVELOPER (INTERNSHIP)

CV. IDS | January 2020 - July 2020

Participate in developing e-learning applications under the name kejar.id using React js programming language, helping to add some new features that are needed:

- 1. Slicing form gma to react is code
- 2. Added some features in betaimda admin app
- 3. Join Ruby on rails bootcamp
- 4. Creating a ruby on rails CRUD tutorial module

# **Education**

Pelita Harapan University
System Informasi | August 2023 - Present

Wikrama 1 Garut Vocation Hight School Software Engineering | 2018 - 2021

Tarbiyatul Huda Islamic Boarding School 2015-2018, City | YYYY - Present Description of the education/course.

# Certification

**Beginner Data Visualization** Dicoding.com

**Backend Programming**Ministry of technology and information & progate

**Public Speaking** IHTC